let modernarts = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Which artist is known for coining the term 'Surrealism'?",
      answer: "Salvador Dali",
      options: ["Pablo Picasso", "Salvador Dali", "Vincent van Gogh", "Henri Matisse"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "Which movement is associated with the use of abstract forms and shapes in art?",
      answer: "Cubism",
      options: ["Impressionism", "Expressionism", "Futurism", "Cubism"],
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "Which artist is known for painting the work 'The Persistence of Memory'?",
      answer: "Salvador Dali",
      options: ["Pablo Picasso", "Salvador Dali", "Vincent van Gogh", "Henri Matisse"],
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'The Scream'?",
      answer: "Edvard Munch",
      options: ["Vincent van Gogh", "Salvador Dali", "Edvard Munch", "Claude Monet"],
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "What movement was associated with the use of bold, bright colors and thick brushstrokes?",
      answer: "Fauvism",
      options: ["Impressionism", "Expressionism", "Fauvism", "Cubism"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "What movement was associated with the use of bright colors, simplified forms, and a focus on movement and speed",
      answer: "Futurism",
      options: ["Impressionism", "Futurism", "Surrealism", "Abstract Expressionism"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Water Lilies'?",
      answer: "Claude Monet",
      options: ["Claude Monet", "Paul Cezanne", "Paul Gauguin", "Paul Klee"]
      
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Les Demoiselles d'Avignon'?",
      answer: "Pablo Picasso",
      options: ["Henri Matisse", "Vincent van Gogh", "Salvador Dali", "Pablo Picasso"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Guernica'?",
      answer: "Pablo Picasso",
      options: ["Claude Mone", "Paul Cezanne", "Pablo Picasso", "Vincent van Gogh"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Which artist is known for creating the sculpture 'The Thinker'?",
      answer: "Auguste Rodin",
      options: ["Auguste Rodin", "Alexander Calder", "Jean Arp", "Henry Moore"]
      
      
    },
  ];

  